{
    "id": "4ddf6017a3f744438b1e7332eb68b593",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How did these things ..................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came about",
                "come about",
                "come off",
                "came off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... an old friend of mine yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came on",
                "came across",
                "came to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That question ..................... . before the committee yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came up",
                "came across",
                "came about"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was …………………. in the prime of his life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cut out",
                "cut off",
                "cut up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His wife’s death ...................... terribly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cut him down",
                "cut him up",
                "cut him out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He seems to be …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well off",
                "pull off",
                "cut off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "At last the truth .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came up",
                "came out",
                "came off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His master .....................… an explanation of his conduct.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "called for",
                "called on",
                "called out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He found it rather difficult to ………………….. to his views.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bring her up",
                "bring her round",
                "bring her out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandmother cannot ………………… past events.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "call out",
                "call on",
                "call up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}